>> Jem Young: 第一类数据库，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: The first type of database,
你可能都听说过一个关系数据库
which you've probably all heard
of is a relational database.
这称为 SQL 数据库或 SQL，安全或结构化查询语言。
That would be known as the SQL database,
or SQL, Safe or Structured Query Language.
我想这取决于你上学的地方，或者你长大的地方。
I think it depends on where you went
to school, or like where you grew up.
如果您说 SQL 或 SQL ，那么不重要。
If you say SQL or SQL, doesn't matter.
就像有人说
Just like some people say integral, and
其他人说积分并不重要
other people say integral,
doesn't really matter.
关系数据库描述实体如何相互关联。
Relational databases describe how
entities relate to each other.
他们总是用桌子和
And they invariably always use tables and
它对于应该如何形成数据有一个非常严格的结构，
it has a very strict structure
on how data should be formed and
应该怎么写，怎么读呢，它真的非常严格。
how should be written and how should be
read, and it's really, really strict.
实际上，如果您使用 MySQL 或 postures 进行过任何类型的 SQL ，或者
In fact, if you've ever done any sort
of SQL using MySQL or postures or
这样就很麻烦的选择了这个表格里的 ID ，
something like that, it can be
cumbersome selects ID from this table,
在此同时使用自己的语言，成为数据库管理员或
left join on this and it's own language,
becoming a database administrator or
数据库专家是它自己的特殊领域。
a database expert is
its own special field.
你真的可以在美国的数据库里学两年。
You literally could go to school for
like two years for just the US databases.
但你需要它因为当你有大量数据时
But you need it because when you
have massive amounts of data,
您需要一种结构化的方法来查询该数据。
you need a structured way
of querying that data.
这就是关系数据库的发明
That's the invention of
relational databases and
结构化查询语言，这是有关如何访问所有这些语言的通用语言。
Structured Query Language, a common
language on how to access all these.
根据您的数据库类型，语言可能会有所变化。
Depending on your type of database,
the language might change a little bit.
因此，像 Costco 那样的语言将使用与 MySQL 不同的语言。
So something like Costco is gonna
use a different language than MySQL.
但一般来说
But generally,
如果你能想象它们的结构，它们的工作方式是一样的。
they kind of all work the same way if
you imagine how they're structured.
我觉得人们用结构查询语言挂的问题
I think the problem that people get
hung up with structure query language
你不能只为数据库写东西我会想办法的
is you can't just write things for
database and like, I'll figure it out.
我们会一起去的
I'll figure it out as we go along.
你要提前有个结构，要有很严格的，
You have to have a structure ahead of
time and you have to have a very strict,
那是什么，是一个模式。
what is that, it's a schema.
当你有一个模式时，它只是说这些是严格的规则。
And when you have a schema,
it's just saying these are strict rules.
所以这一栏是主宰者的一员
So this column for
is a member of front of masters,
这将会是一个布尔值类型，将由 1 或 0 表示。
that's gonna be a Boolean type,
which is gonna be represented by 1 or 0.
这一切都不可能发生
And it can't be anything else.
如果你想写点别的
And if you try to write
something else to it,
它会失败的因为它会随着时间的推移而保持严格的结构
it's gonna fail, because it's all about
maintaining a strict structure over time.
现在，关系数据库中的 SQL 是第一次，但是
Now, SQL in relational databases
were the first time, but
随着时间的推移，您可能听到了非关系数据库或 NoSQL 数据库。
over time you've probably heard of non
relational databases, or NoSQL databases.
当我们想到纯文档存储时，这些都是我们在想的。
These are more what we were thinking about
when we think of pure document storage.
他们通常是数据不可知论者
They're generally data agnostic,
他们不关心你放进去的那种数据，没有结构。
they don't care what kind of data you put
in there, there's no structure to it.
或者如果有一个结构，它是一个非常松散的结构。
Or if there is a structure,
it's a very, very loose structure.
因此， NoSQL 数据库或非关系的示例是着名的
So an example of a NoSQL database or
non relational be redis is the famous
一个， MongoDB 用于记录商店或 elasticsearch。
one, MongoDB used to document store or
elasticsearch.
关于非关系数据库的问题，我觉得很有趣的是
The thing about non relational database
which I find really interesting is they
都有自己在世界上独一无二的地方
all have their own kinda
unique place in the world.
所以红红真的很擅长做现金数据库
So redis is really good
at it as a cash database.
Redis 只是一个关键的价值存储。
Redis is just a key value store.
给定一个键，这是一个值。
Given a key, here's a value.
我不会这么简单的说只要你的查询就会变得很乱
I won't say as simple as it can get cuz
like it the queries can get pretty messy.
但如果如何保存数据，我的名字是吉姆，我的姓是年轻的。
But if terms of how to save data,
my name is Jim, my last name is young.
这就像得到一样简单
That's as simple as it gets.
因此，如果需要，我们可以创建具有编辑的高速缓存服务器，
So we can create a caching server
with redis if we needed to,
我们之前谈过高速缓存的事
and we spoke earlier about caching.
执行此操作的一种方法是使用 rediis 数据库。
One way of doing that is
with a redis database.
另一方面，蒙戈是一家文件商店。
Mongo, on the other hand,
is a document store.
所以它是专门储存文件的
So it's made to specifically
store documents.
所以认为一个具有任意 JSON Blob 的密钥，以及有关 JSON 的信息
So think a key with an arbitrary JSON
blob, and the thing about JSON is it
并不一定会有同样的结构
doesn't necessarily have
the same structure all the time.
它不是一个结构的符号，它有一个结构，但是它很松散。
It's not a structured notation per se,
has a structure but it's pretty loose.
我们是 MongoDB ，只是把数据转储在数据仓库里，然后把它拉出来。
We're MongoDB is about just dumping data
into a data store and pulling it back out.
还有一些你可能听说过的是亚马逊的红移。
Some other ones you might have heard
of would be redshift on Amazon.
这是一个非常庞大的规模数据库。
That's a very large and
like petabyte scale database.
基于旧版本的 Postgres ，现在它已经转移了。
Built on the old version of Postgres,
and it's now since shifted.
您都听过或使用过的其他数据库是什么 ?
What are some other databases you
all have heard of or have used?
这里有很多
There's a lot.
>> 扬声器 2: Firebase。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Firebase.
>> Jem Young: Firebase，我不知道这是否是一个数据库。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Firebase,
I don't know if that's a database per se.
是吗
It is?
好吧今天学到了新东西
Okay, learnt something new today.
我觉得这更有联系
I thought it's more of
a type of connection.
>> 演讲者 3: 那是一个数据库和实时数据。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Well, that's it's
a database coupled with the live data.
>> Jem Young: 是的，认为更像是某种形式的协议，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, thought is
more of like a protocol of sorts,
但是- >> 扬声器 3: 它是非关系数据库
but-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It's non relational database
在谷歌的云中
in Google's cloud.
> > Jem Young: 嘿，太棒了
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Hey, that's awesome.
我不知道那个火碱很好的例子。
I didn't know that firebase good example.
还有其他的吗
Any other ones?
>> 演讲者 3: CouchDB。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: CouchDB.
>> Jem Young: CouchDB，任何其他 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: CouchDB, any other ones?
>> 演讲者 3:PouchDB。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: PouchDB.
>> Jem Young: PouchDB，是的，其他任何与担保 DB 的押韵吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: PouchDB, yeah,
anything else that rhymes with ouch DB?
>> [LAUGH] >> Jem Young: 实际上有一个数据库
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: There's actually a database
已构建到名为 IndexedDB的浏览器中。
built into your browser called IndexedDB.
没有很多人使用它，但它是可以使用的。
Not a lot of people use it,
but it's available.
因为我们想，哎，我们都有这些数据库，
Because we thought, hey,
we have all these databases,
为什么不使用构建到浏览器中的数据库 ?
why not just use a database
built into the browser?
嗯。
Yes.
>> 演讲者 3: 不是区块链数据库， kinda?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Aren't
blockchains databases, kinda?
>> Jem Young: 我不知道我是否称区块链为数据库本身。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I don't know if I
call blockchain a database per se.
这取决于我们如何定义数据库。
It depends how we're defining database.
我们的意思是它是数据的原始存储。
We're saying like it's
a raw store of data.
是的但我不会说这就像变量本身
Yes, but
I wouldn't say it's like variable per se.
它不是被构建为变量的。
It's not built to be variable.
你我觉得查询你要经过整个区块链才能找到什么
You I think the query, you have to run
through the entire blockchain to find what
据我所知你要找的人
you're looking for, as far as I know.
非关系数据库方面有哪些吸引力 ?
What's fascinating about the non
relational database side?
NoSQL 端是不断创建新数据库的人员。
The NoSQL side is people
are constantly creating new databases.
因为他们有非常独特的情况需要速度和速度
Because they have some very unique
case that requires like speed or
一致性，或类似非关系型
consistency, or something like that,
versus the non relational
更能有效地查询数据的数据库，以及
databases which are more about being
able to query data efficiently, and
能够快速了解情况，快速修改事物。
be able to look things up quickly and
modify things quickly.
而非关系则需要更多的时间。
Whereas non relational,
it's gonna take a little bit more time.
如果你只是想尽快把文件取出来
If you're just trying to get
documents out as fast as possible,
这个可能比较快一点，一般来讲，
this could be a little bit faster,
generally speaking.
数据库有问题吗
Any questions on databases?
我们刚刚飞过来了
We just flew through those.
我不想做任何具体因为它真的取决于你的
I didn't wanna get into any specific
one because it really depends on your
用例。
used case.